Guide to the Collected editions of standard authors, ca. 1829-1903.
Collected editions of standard authors
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collected editions of standard authors, ca. 1829-1903.
8003
25 cubic ft.
Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Multi-volume sets in decorative bindings.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Multi-volume sets in decorative bindings. Collected authors include: Robert Burns, James Fenimore Cooper, William Cowper, Charles Dickens, Alexander Dumas, Ralph Waldo Emerson, John Fiske, Johann Wolfgang von Goethe, Nathaniel Hawthorne, Oliver Wendell Holmes, Victor Hugo, John Ingram, Washington Irving, Charles Lamb, Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, James Russell Lowell, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Thomas Moore, Francis Parkman, Walter Scott, Eugene Sue, Lord Alfred Tennyson, and John Greenleaf Whittier.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie, Publisher; Philadelphia; Vol. I (Box 1)
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie, Publisher; Philadelphia; Vol. II (Box 1)
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie, Publisher; Philadelphia; Vol. III (Box 1)
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie, Publisher; Philadelphia; Vol. IV (Box 1)
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie, Publisher; Philadelphia; Vol. V (Box 1)
- Ingram, John H.; The Tales and Poems of Edgar Allen Poe; George Barrie,; Philadelphia; Vol. VI (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The Beginnings of New England; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings VI (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The Dutch and Quaker Colonies in America I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings VII (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The Dutch and Quaker Colonies in America II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings VIII (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; New France and New England; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings IX (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The American Revolution I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings X (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The American Revolution II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings XI (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; The Critical Period of American History; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Historical Writings XII (Box 1)
- Fiske, John; Civil Government in the United States; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1902; John Fiske’s Miscellaneous Writings XII (Box 1)
- Macaulay, Lord; The History of England: From the Accession of James the Second; Harper & Brothers; New York; 1879; Vol. 1 (Box 1)
- Trevelyan, G. Otto; The Life and Letters of Lord Macaulay; Harper & Brothers; New York; Vol. 1 (Box 1)
- Trevelyan, G. Otto; The Life and Letters of Lord Macaulay; Harper & Brothers; New York; Vol. 2 (Box 1)
- Taine, H.A.; History of English Literature; Holt & Williams; New York; 1887; Vol. 1 (Box 2)
- Taine, H.A.; History of English Literature; Holt & Williams; New York; 1887; Vol. 2 (Box 2)
- Lane, Edward William; The Thousand and One Nights (The Arabian Nights’ Entertainments); Routledge, Warne and Routledge; London; Vol I (Box 2)
- Lane, Edward William; The Thousand and One Nights (The Arabian Nights’ Entertainments); Routledge, Warne and Routledge; London; Vol II (Box 2)
- Lane, Edward William; The Thousand and One Nights (The Arabian Nights’ Entertainments); Routledge, Warne and Routledge; London; Vol III (Box 2)
- Whiston, William; The Works of Flavius Josephus; Herny G. Bohn; London; 1862; Vol. I (Box 2)
- Whiston, William; The Works of Flavius Josephus; Herny G. Bohn; London; 1862; Vol. II (Box 2)
- D’Abrantes, The Duchess; Memoirs of Napoleon, His Court and Family; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1870; Vol. I (Box 2)
- D’Abrantes, The Duchess; Memoirs of Napoleon, His Court and Family; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1870; Vol. II (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. I (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. II (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. III (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. IV (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. V (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. VI (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. VII (Box 2)
- Mitford, John; The Works of John Milton: In Verse and Prose; Bickers and Bush; London; 1863; Vol. VIII (Box 2)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Autocrat of the Breakfast-Table; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. I (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Professor at the Breakfast-Table; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. II (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Poet at the Breakfast-Table; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. III (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Over the Teacups; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. IV (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; Elsie Venner; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. V (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; The Guardian Angel; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. VI (Box 3)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell; A Mortal Antipathy; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Holmes’s Works Vol. VII (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Nature, Addresses and Lectures; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. I (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Essays I; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. II (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Essays II; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. III (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Representative Men; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. IV (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; English Traits; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. V (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Conduct of Life; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. VI (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Society and Solitude; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. VII (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Letters and Social Aims; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. VIII (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Poems; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. IX (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Lectures and Biographical Sketches; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. X (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Miscellanies; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. XI (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Natural History of Intellect; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. XII (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Memoir I; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. XIII (Box 3)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo; Memoir II; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; Emerson’s Works Vol. XIV (Box 3)
- Scott, Walter; Waverley; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1829; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. I (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Waverley; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1830; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. II (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Guy Mannering; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. III (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Guy Mannering; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. IV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Antiquary; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. V (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Antiquary; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. VI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Rob Roy; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. VII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Rob Roy; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. VIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Old Mortality; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. IX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Old Mortality; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. X (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Mid-Lothian; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Mid-Lothian; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Lammermoor; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Lammermoor; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1831; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XIV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Montrose; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1830; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Ivanhoe; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XVI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Ivanhoe; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XVII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Monastery; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XVIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Monastery; Cadell & Company; Edinburgh; 1832; Scott’s Waverley Novels Vol. XIX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Periodical Criticism; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Periodical Criticism; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XIX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Periodical Criticism; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Periodical Criticism; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXIV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1838; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXVI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXVII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Tales of a Grandfather; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; 1836; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXVIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Demonology and Witchcraft; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXIX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Religious Discourses Etc.; Walter Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Prose Works Vol. XXX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Border Minstrelsy; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. I (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Border Minstrelsy; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. II (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Border Minstrelsy; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. III (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Border Minstrelsy; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. IV (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Sir Tristrem; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. V (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Lay of Last Minstrel; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. VI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Marmion; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. VII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Lady of the Lake; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. VIII (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Rokeby; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. IX (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Lord of the sles; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. X (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Bridal of Triermain Etc.; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. XI (Box 4)
- Scott, Walter; Dramas; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; Scott’s Political Works Vol. XII (Box 4)
- Dickens, Charles; Edwin Drood; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1871; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Master Humphrey’s Clock; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1869; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Uncommercial Traveller; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Christmas Stories I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Christmas Stories II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Barnaby Rudge I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Barnaby Rudge II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Barnaby Rudge III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Great Expectations I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Great Expectations II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Oliver Twist I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Oliver Twist II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Hard Times I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Hard Times II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; American Notes I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; American Notes II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Two Cities I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Two Cities II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Nicholas Nickleby I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Nicholas Nickleby II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Nicholas Nickleby III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Nicholas Nickleby IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Martin Chuzzlewit I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Martin Chuzzlewit II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Martin Chuzzlewit III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Martin Chuzzlewit IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Little Dorrit I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Little Dorrit II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Little Dorrit III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Little Dorrit IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Bleak House I; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Bleak House II; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Bleak House III; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Bleak House IV; Hurd and Houghton; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Sketches I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dickens, Charles; Sketches II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1864; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 5)
- Dumas, Alexandre; La Comtesse De Charny IV; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; La Comtesse De Charny III; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Page of the Duke Savoy; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Regent’s Daughter; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Forty-Five; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Companions of Jehu; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Black, The Story of a Dog; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Horoscope; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Agenor De Mauleon; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Three Musketeers; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Sylvandire; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The Whites and the Blues; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; La Dame De Monsoreau; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Ascanio; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Le Chevalier De Maison-Rouge; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The War of Women; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Marguerite De Valois; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 6)
- Whittier, John; Narrative and Legendary Poems; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Poetical Works of John Greenleaf Whittier I (Box 7)
- Whittier, John; Poems of Nature, Reminiscent and Religious Poems; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Poetical Works of John Greenleaf Whittier II (Box 7)
- Whittier, John; Anti-Slavery Poems, Songs of Labor and Reform; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Poetical Works of John Greenleaf Whittier III (Box 7)
- Whittier, John; Personal Poems, Tent on the Beach at Sundown; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Poetical Works of John Greenleaf Whittier IV (Box 7)
- Whittier, John; Margaret Smith’s Journal Tales and Sketches; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Prose Works of John Greenleaf Whittier I (Box 7)
- Whittier, John; Portraits and Sketches, Historical Papers; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1892; The Prose Works of John Greenleaf Whittier II (Box 7)
- Hawthorne, Julian; Nathaniel Hawthorne and His Wife; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1884; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne XV (Box 7)
- Farnham, Charles Haight; A Life of Francis Parkman; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1901 (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; Pioneers of France in the New World; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman I (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; Frontenac and New France Under Louis XIV vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman X (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; A Half-Century of Conflict vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman XI (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; A Half-Century of Conflict vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman XII (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; Montcalm and Wolfe vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman XIII (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; Montcalm and Wolfe vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; 1897; The Works of Francis Parkman XIV (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; Montcalm and Wolfe vol. III; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XV (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; The Conspiracy of Pontiac vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XVI (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; The Conspiracy of Pontiac vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XVII (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; The Conspiracy of Pontiac vol. III; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XVIII (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; The Oregon Trail vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XIX (Box 7)
- Parkman, Francis; The Oregon Trail vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; 1898; The Works of Francis Parkman XX (Box 7)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Hawt-Home 13; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Hood-Juli 14; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Just-Lowe 15; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Lowt-Miln 16; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Milt-Nord 17; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Norr-Pope 18; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Port-Ryan 19; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Rydb-Shel 20; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Shel-Stol 21; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Ston-Thom 22; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Thom-Walw 23; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Warb-Zwin 24; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- The Ridpath of Universal Literature vol. Index 25; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 8)
- Baker, Charles H., Jr.; The Gentleman’s Companion vol I & II; Crown Publishers; New York; 1946 (Box 8)
- Irving, Washington; Life of George Washington vol. I; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York 1869 (Box 8)
- Irving, Washington; The Life and Voyages of Christopher Columbus vol. I; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 8)
- Irving, Washington; The Life and Voyages of Christopher Columbus vol. II; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 8)
- Thackery, William Makepeace; Henry Esmond; Thomas Y. Crowell & Co.; New York (Box 8)
- Irving, Washington; The Life and Letters of Washington Irving vol. II; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Spanish Papers; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; The Adventures of Captain Bonneville, U.S.A.; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Biographies and Miscellanies; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; The Crayton Miscellany; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Oliver Goldsmith; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Astoria; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; The Sketch-Book of Geoffrey Crayton, Gent.; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Chronicles of the Conquest of Granada; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Wolfert’s Roost and Other Papers; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Irving, Washington; Nickerbocker’s New York; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; “My Novel” on Varieties in English Life vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; “My Novel” on Varieties in English Life vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)